威尔 · 森特斯: 让我们去找丹，去吧，伙计。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's go to Dan,
go ahead man.
阿丹: 告诉我，如果我进入杂草，但回到最后一个例子在哪里
&gt;&gt; Dan: Tell me if I'm getting in the
weeds, but back to the last example where
我们有一千毫秒的暂停时间，它只是在等待。
we have the thousand millisecond
timeout and it's just waiting.
事件循环只是检查。
That event loop is just checking.
那整整一秒钟的通话记录呢？
Is there anything on the call sack for
that entire second?
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，当然。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, absolutely.
它要做的就是继续评估是否有代码要运行,
The way it's gonna do it is continue
to assess if there's any code to run,
然后在幕后循环，比较
and then each loop behind the scenes,
it's comparing what
计时器显示的是等待的时间，等待的时间是当前的时间。
the timer says is the wait time
to what is the current time.
它会不断地检查时间是否足够一旦它检查完,
And it's gonna constantly check, is enough
time passed, and as soon as it has,
它会抓住那个函数并执行它。
it's gonna grab that function and
execute it.
那个事件循环是不是和你的浏览器一样持续运行
&gt;&gt; Dan: Is that event loop running
constantly as long as your browser
是开着的吗？
is open?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 只要我们的应用程序还在运行，是的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: As long as our
application's running, yeah, yeah.
Peter 说吧。
Peter, go ahead.
彼得: 如果，锁一秒代替，运行我们的循环为
&gt;&gt; Peter: If, Lock for one second
was instead, running our loop for
500 milliseconds and then called Portillo and ran for
500 milliseconds and
then called Portillo and ran for
再过500毫秒，我们能听到你好吗？
another 500 milliseconds,
would we get that hello?
先是“我” ，然后计时器又用完了一个“你好” ？
And then @me first, and
then when the timer ran out another hello?
威尔 · 森特斯: 如果我们打电话给印刷公司打招呼,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well if
we are calling print hello,
你说我们要打电话给 printHello 在1号区域内。
you say we're calling printHello
inside of blockFor1Sec.
彼得: 是的，威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，当然。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Yeah,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, absolutely.
所以如果我们用传统的方式称呼 printHello,
So if we were calling printHello
in the conventional sense,
我们是不是命令那个指纹去运行？
and it's did we command
that print hello to run?
所以它在一个区块里，我们自己编写了调用 printHello。
So it's inside a blockFor1Sec,
we'd written call printHello ourselves.
这是同步代码，这是常规代码，所有典型的全局代码,
Well that's synchronous code, that's
regular, all your typical global code,
不是全局代码，是1秒区域内的代码。
not global code, code inside blockFor1Sec.
当我们告诉它运行时，它就会运行。
That will just run when we tell it to run.
这就是我们，我们有没有在 printHello 的结尾加上任何括号？
This is when we, did we put any
parens on the end of printHello?
现在设置超时。
With set timeout now.
我们将依靠设置超时来运行这个函数
We're going to rely with set timeout
on that function to be able to run for
我们，我们需要非常，非常严格的规则，当这可以自动运行。
us and we need very, very strict
rules when that can be auto run.